jigsawplanet.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes Jigsaw Planet's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. Jigsaw Planet receives your information through our various web sites, APIs, services and third-parties ("Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Jigsaw Planet in the United States or any other country where Jigsaw Planet operates.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

## Information Collection and Use

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or reconfigure a Jigsaw Planet account, you provide some personal information, such as your username, password, and email address. Username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on the home page and explore pages. Some Services, such as the home page, public user gallery and explore pages, do not require registration.

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain and pages visited. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.

**Links:** Jigsaw Planet may keep track of how you interact with links by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Jigsaw Planet may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. Cookies are stored in your web browser for 180 days or less from your last visit. Current versions of web browsers offer enhanced user controls of cookies (disabling, removing).

**Third Party Services:** We use advertisements provided by Google adSense to support our site. Google uses cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. In particular, Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie to enable it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/). 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your Jigsaw Planet account.

**Service Providers:** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

**Law and Harm:** We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Jigsaw Planet's rights or property.

**Business Transfers:** In the event that Jigsaw Planet is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your created puzzles or the number of users who played a particular puzzle or a list of users who played a particular puzzle.

## Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

## Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us by Contact. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://www.jigsawplanet.com/?rc=privacy. If we make a change to this policy that, at our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via Jigsaw Planet News or e-mail to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

Effective: December 06, 2011
